It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'm not dead.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true.
Don't you feel it? I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away. The great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you. Only win out.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow. Go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life. It's your light.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going. Out of day.
You make my day every day.
Hey, what happened to the reinforcements
headed to the eastern port?
They, uh, seem to have run into
a bit of trouble along the way.
And what does that mean?
Their bullets and gunpowder
have gone missing.
Unfortunately, all of our other
weapons, like swords, axes,
and knives and such, are missing as well.
I can only assume they
were stolen by someone.
And that's just the start.
The warships can't sail from the port.
Because they're all stuck to each other!
like someone sewed them together.
You can't sew iron with thread?
This is insane!
Grab something and cut it!
Hurry!
We can't!
Our knives are missing!
Also, the soldiers who collapsed
earlier are still paralyzed.
How can you possibly
screw things up this much?
We're sorry, sir.
Do you know how many criminals
we're dealing with here?
You can't let them get away.
Figure something out.
We'll do our best.
I'm worried I might be taking
too much from them today.
Mauji, you're sure this is okay, right?
I don't want them to get paralyzed.
They've all been so generous.
Don't worry.
We got permission, of course.
From heroes.
Please carry on, princess.
Okay, then I'll keep it up.
We still have a whole ton
of heavy injuries to heal.
I know you're in the middle of
this, but we need to go now.
I'll only be a second.
Okay, I'll wait.
According to the citizens,
we asked these strange occurrences
are the work of fairies.
seems to be something they're used to.
Are you stupid?
They're obviously lying to you.
I'll keep looking into it.
Barrier!
That hold against him?
Wouldn't be a barrier if it didn't.
We're not exactly weak.
We can hold till Mr.
Luffy and Law show up. Yeah!
Did the fight start already?
Would you like some crackers, perhaps?
No, thanks.
Just start talking.
A boy with white lead disease.
So there was a survivor from Whitetown.
He resents everything in this world.
Feels like I'm watching my
older brother when he was a kid.
He has my sympathy, but there's
no cure for white lead disease.
Don't get involved too much
or you'll give yourself away.
I know. Don't worry.
I won't forget what I'm here to do.
I'll stop my brother at any cost.
He won't lay a finger on Dressrosa.
We've lost a lot of good Marines.
But it was different when I lost him.
He was special to me.
We met when he was a child.
I thought of him as my own son.
He was as honest as they came, with
an unshakable sense of justice.
Naturally, he had my absolute trust.
Regardless, he did lie to me once.
In the very end.
I heard a landing unit here.
Among the dead, there's
a Don Quixote exec.
His codename is Corazon.
I've sent a picture of him.
Could you confirm?
Rosanante, what were you
doing on that island?
He betrayed me.
That's how it felt, at least.
but I know he must have
had a reason. There were
four things that were
lost during that incident
the barrel's pirate crew the life
of poor rozenante the op-op fruit
and of course the young
boy who was with the don
quixote family then the
one with the white lead
disease. Yeah, that
was me I
thought so so
when Rosenante stepped
away from his mission
for that half of a year before he died it
was to help you, wasn't
it? That's right. He took
me to countless hospitals but that failed
so he set his sights
on the op-op fruit and
when things went south
since he meant so much
to me i must ask what
exactly did he die for
my life everything even though
we weren't able to leave together
like we planned and gave me back
my freedom and my will to live.
I'm forever in his debt.
That's why I carried this out, to take
down Doflamingo and avenge his death.
But now, I wonder if that
was my fate as a D all along.
And he knew.
D.
The same secret name is Straw Hat, though
I still don't know what that amounts to.
Since you used to be the fleet admiral,
perhaps you can tell me, what's
the meaning behind that letter?
Don't play dumb with me!
I can tell you one thing, Rosanante
didn't know any more about Dee than you.
In other words, that wasn't the
reason why he saved your life.
He didn't need a reason,
he did it out of love.
I love you, kid.
Another D, huh?
It's true, they always
follow a checkered fate.
Shame I'm not on active duty.
I would have locked you in a cell
where we could have had a nice,
long chat about this.
You're the only person I can share all
of my fond memories of Rosanante with.
How unfortunate that you're a pirate.
If you want to honor his memory,
you can do the same as I've done.
Never mind revenge.
Just keep him in your heart, always.
Live the life that you desire.
One that makes you happy.
He fought to set you free.
That's what he would want.
What the hell?
Interesting.
Whoa! What?
It's exploding!
Get out of there!
That's messed up!
What's causing this?
The buildings are lifting
straight into the air.
They're not going to drop, are they?
It looks like they're all
going to the port in the east.
Ladies and gentlemen,
do my allies deceive me.
Is this the work of a god for
giant invisible birds, perhaps?
No.
There's only one person on the island, more
possibly in the world, capable of this.
This is the work of
Navy Admiral Fuki Dorry!
Pardon me, but since you don't
need all this debris and rubble,
I thought I might put it to good use.
Those infernal pirates are the ones who
made this mess, so let them feel its weight.
So now, what we're screwed?
How do we fight back?
One thing's for
certain—we're going to need
a much bigger barrier
or a different strategy.
That's crazy!
Come on—they're shooting cheese.
What is
that in the sky?
Oh, it's no time to be screaming in
terror—we gotta go help the go help the
It can't be.
This is mad.
That's how he intends to
capture all the pirates?
They'll be dead.
No one can survive that.
This is a disaster.
Their escape fell apart so quickly.
Lucy!
Vice Admiral Bastille.
Hey, Bastille!
Uh, yes. Hello, Tsuru. My apologies.
I was overwhelmed for a second.
Well, still need those reinforcements?
No, we're good.
All units, withdraw!
We no longer need
reinforcements at the port!
Evacuate from the east
side of the kingdom!
Any civilians you see should also
be evacuated to a safe location!
Hey guys, no place in this kingdom
is safe from this. Set sail!
Now all right, then Trafal—we've
been waiting for you in Straw Hat!
Where were you two?
We're
under the ship.
It's time to sail out.
Hey,
finally!
He's here! Luffy!
We
gotta host some ass! ass Mr.
Luffy
Took his time.
That's everybody.
Let's move out! Mr.
Luffy, there's an angry
Fujitora in your way
Mr. Luffy,
Everybody's making a run for it now. Just
dodge him, be careful. Just dodge him?
Hey, Gambler Man, do you remember me?
Of course, I've been waiting for you.
Get ready for a fight.
You've got one coming.
Don't come, Mr. Elephant.
Mr.
Luffy, why?
We're supposed to be running away.
Don't pick a fight with that guy.
Being in Thunder isn't good enough.
Why should I run away?
Why should I back down from the Navy?
I did that two years ago.
But I'm done with that now!
I don't care if it's a Navy Admiral
or one of the Four Emperors!
I gotta beat them all someday!
Because if I don't...
Then I'll never be King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna punch you!
I'm gonna...
A bullet!
We need to get out of here,
but I want to watch this fight.
You really are a nuisance.
Should we fight him too?
Now I'm gonna stop you!
Kum-Kum!
Hop!
I'm on board with the
stuff that Luffy said.
Like calling out all his moves?
Is that some kind of
weird power play or what?
I'm gonna!
It's you!
I'm in push!
So sorry about that!
Got carried away there.
No need to concern yourself.
It was no threat to me.
Okay, you ready, old man?
I'm going to punch you!
Now a kick and a punch!
Now punching really fast!
A shove!
Headbots!
A big stomp!
First he makes me super-heavy,
and then he makes me super-light?
That looks bad.
I get that you're being a badass, but
I really think you should run away!
No more running!
Not anymore!
I see.
With your strength,
that's reasonable enough.
I do admire your spirit.
I'm gonna punch you!
But this strategy of yours,
I find rather confusing!
Why are you announcing
all of your attacks?
Are you taking pity on me?
Have you forgotten?
I'm a Navy Admiral!
I'm feared as a monster far and wide!
I haven't achieved this level of strength
only to suffer your misguided sympathy!
Are you troubled to see a
blind man on the battlefield?
Does my prowess not speak for itself?
If you'd hoped to aggravate
me, then you've succeeded.
You can laugh your way to the
grave while I take your head.
Oh, shut up!
No matter how strong you are,
if I attack you and you can't see it
coming, then that's like cheating!
You're Navy!
But that doesn't mean I don't like you!
Hey, what are you laughing at, you jerk?
I'm going to kick you!
What good is your sympathy?
Your act of mercy will gain you nothing.
I'm going to punch you a bunch.
I thought you were a man of conviction,
but it seems you're strung along
by some whimsical nonsense.
Here comes a punch!
Really hard.
When a man enters a battle like this.
No matter his side, he
has a standing to uphold.
That leaves no room for pity.
No matter how sincere your feelings are.
They have no place in this struggle.
I don't desire this fight,
but I believe in my duty.
And I won't be suffice like you. No!
Gravity Blade!
Raging Tiger!
Look, there he is, Harrood!
Hey!
Put me down!
Take him to the ship!
Nice try, Luffy.
Now it's my turn.
We're done with that!
It's time to run away, Mr. Zoro.
We got this whole operation
we're pulling off here.
Oh, yeah?
So, uh, are we all cramming
onto one ship at the port?
Because that's kind of dangerous.
Not aboard.
Our destination is further out.
Just look ahead.
Huh?
Whoa, what the heck?
You've got like a whole
fleet forming a line.
How far out does this go?
Over three miles.
The ships that we'll be taking
are hidden in the fog ahead.
We'll cross this connecting
bridge made by my
Aunt Maria See a fleet and
board the ships at sea.
Hey!
I'm not done fighting the
old guy yet! Let me go!
Can you be reasonable just this once?
I said I wouldn't run!
I gotta fight!
We have a mission.
You can fight next time.
If you think I'll simply let
you escape, you're mistaken.
Whether you fight or you flee, it's
already too late for you, Straw Hat.
I know how you must feel
right now, Straw Hat.
Although I cannot see
the havoc I have wrought,
I know it looms heavily before your eyes.
A dark sky that suffocates
any hope for escape.
The moment you try to set sail, this
rubble will fall like an endless rain.
Sinking every ship into the abyss below.
Surely you must know, even if by
some miracle you do escape me?
The four emperors will
hound your every step.
By defeating Joker, you've
put a target on your back!
Your life will be a living hell
until at last they claim your neck.
You took pity on me for my blindness.
But the truth is, this was an
injury that I brought upon myself.
These eyes were closed
by my own actions because
they saw too many things
that I didn't care for.
Things that I wished they hadn't.
All right.
If you're so intent on making your way
to hell, then allow me to guide you.
Give us back Rebecca, Lucy!
We got to our hill, dammit! What happened?
He's dead.
His kingdom has made her suffer enough!
Whatever you're planning,
we're going to stop it!
I'm sorry to say, there
are only criminals ahead.
You'll find people are making a
terrible mistake by coming here.
Allow me to handle this.
If you don't stop me...
Move it, Navy!
We don't need your help!
This is our kingdom!
We'll take care of the pirates ourselves!
They're running to Strahat.
There are thousands of them!
What?
What's all that commotion back there?
The people of Dressrosa, but
what do you think they want?
Better prepare yourself, Lucy!
Lucy!
We're gonna get you!
Get the ship, chase them out to sea!
What is this?
Lucy!
You can't get away!
Despite their words, I don't
sense a hint of animosity.
Give back Rebecca or
we'll give you a wallop!
Hey you guys!
I saw Rebecca at the top of the hill!
She's safe with Kairos!
don't worry we know just have fun
nobody talks about it but kiros
is rebecca's father she's probably
going to live with him from now on
they used to live together
as a family with scarlet
in that little cottage on
the hill all the adults
in the kingdom have known
that for 16 years now
of course we knew the truth
about the fairies too,
but we kept the secret to protect them.
Really?
Anyway, those pirates saved their kingdom,
so now it's our turn to save them.
If we stick close to Lucy, Fujitora won't
be able to drop the rubble from the sky.
We're coming, Lucy.
You better get ready.
You're in real trouble now.
You're a fool, Straw
Hat, but an honest one.
I suppose I shouldn't be surprised
that everyone wants to take your side.
What kind of a man are you, I wonder?
What's the color of your
hair, the shape of your eyes?
What does your smile look like?
What a pity.
Wish I could use these eyes one last time
to see the face of a man like you.
I'm sure it's filled to
the brim with kindness.
Now, what shall I do with this
unsightly weapon I've raised?
I look like quite the fool.
I am gonna murder you!
All our work with Doflamingo is screwed,
thanks to your meddling, Straw Hat!
Don't let him escape Dressrosa alive!
And what about King Rick?
If he's back, our business
is gonna suffer for it!
We'll kill the Straw Hat
and all his pals too.
There'll be no one left to stop us.
After that, dress rosa
will be our playground.
All right, we'll form an alliance—a
fleet of pirates united by our hatred!
hatred
No mercy! No escape!
Take his head!
All marines have retreated, but the
citizens are running to the port!
What the hell is Isho doing down there?
Are you gonna keep that
rubble in the sky all day?
Check this out!
Oh, man, it's huge!
Is that an awesome ship or what?
It's not even yours, okay.
We better get aboard before the
sky falls on us or whatever!
I'll show you my ship later.
You're gonna flip out! Draw hat!
I have four friends who are
giant mercenaries like me.
I want to reach out to all
the other giant tribes and.
form a crew.
Then we'll shake the
foundations of this world,
just like the famous giant pirates did
in the past.
Remember, Luffy?
That was Master Dorry and Brogy's
crew in their glory days. That's cool.
He'll be a good rival then.
Well, I can't wait to see
your crew when it's done.
Yeah, and I can't wait
to see Elbaf someday.
My aunt to Maria fleet is at your call.
Our force is number 56 ships, you know.
Should come in handy.
Is that so? Lofi-land!
We just got permission from our chief.
We want to join up with you. To join up,
I won't lose to anyone in a boxing ring.
but if I can't take on pirates, I'll
never be a true champion I agreed.
So we're teaming up.
We'll see where the waves take us.
Hey, don't forget about us.
We've got your back, pal.
This idiot is letting me
on a ship for some reason.
I'm helping you out Call me
captain at least as for you.
I still have more experience
as a pirate So when we team up,
I'm sure to be the popular one
I'm not asking for help from anybody.
You guys can do whatever you want.
Well, that's the thing.
We kind of hit it off
while we were all staying
at the palace and
decided to run with this.
Let me introduce the team.
We chose the order by drawing straws.
First, the beautiful
pirates with 75 members.
Their captain is Cavendish
of the White Oars.
Next, the Bartolomeo Club with 56 members.
Their captain is Bartolomeo the Cannibal.
Then the Hapasui Army
a thousand men strong.
Their 13th leader is Don Sai.
Next, the Triple X Gym Fighting
Alliance with four members.
They're led by Destruction Cannon Edeo.
Then we have the Taunta
Corps with 200 members.
Their leader is Leo the Warrior.
Then we have the soon-to-be giant
pirates, five members and growth.
Their captain is Hyrudin.
Last but not least, Commodore of the
Yontemaria fleet with 4,300 members.
The adventuring pioneer, Orlumbus.
That's me.
Uh, what's wrong?
A force of 5 ,600 total! Mr.
Luffy, exchange cups with
the leaders of each crew.
We'll drink ritual sake as father and son!
Okay, how does that work?
In a crew, the boss is the
father and his men are the sons.
As leader of the Straw Hat Pirates, we
humbly ask you to take us under your wing.
So, do you accept?
Let us exchange the vows
of father and son with Mr.
Luffy as our new boss.
And us as his followers.
You gotta drink it, Mr.
Luffy
I think I'll pass.
Go figure.
I'm not into sake.
No, it's not for taste. It's a vow.
And listen, you're gonna be
famous after this whole thing.
Meaning a bunch of bad dudes
are gonna wanna try to kill ya.
It doesn't matter how strong you are.
Nobody can win against numbers like that.
You need backup.
That's where we come in.
You saved us, so we'll save you.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Yeah, but if I drink this stuff?
I'll be the big captain guy of
some grand fleet, is that right?
Uh, yeah.
With 5 ,600 followers, you'd be one of
the most impressive pirates on the seas.
I mean, you're gonna be king of the
pirates eventually, no doubt about it.
But it's a big world, so if you want to
conquer it, then you gotta think big.
He doesn't care. Give it up.
You're wasting your time. Huh?
So, put this in a beer mug.
I'll drink it.
I said it's not for taste, it's for a vow!
Why, Straw Hat?
A massive military force
could be at your command.
The men who stand before
you are almighty warriors,
and yet we would have been
undone without your help.
Someday you'll find yourself
in the same situation.
Not my style!
Huh?
What's with that look?
Anyway, are people getting ready
for a party? Cause I smell food.
That's great.
Just change the subject.
You're pissing me off, Straw Hat.
Listen,
you should be grateful that a star like
me is willing to fly under your flag.
Let's force him to drink it.
I know you saved us, but we're
strong enough to kick your ass.
I thought he was the boss.
Don't be so rude.
Here's the thing.
I want to be the king of the pirates.
I don't need to be some big shot.
Huh?
Even for him, that's dumb.
Damn, that's good stuff. Knew it.
You's a cop!
That's so gross!
Ooh, me next.
I want some too.
How about this?
If I'm ever in trouble,
I'll call you guys for help.
And I know you'll save me, because that's
what friends do for each other, right?
I don't have to be a big shot
or have a whole fleet for that.
And if you're ever in trouble call us.
I'm happy to help anytime
I couldn't have beat
Mingo without you guys.
So we're friends for life
You know.
It took a second, but I get it now.
And I think I understand what it means
for you to be king of the pirates.
It's not about being big, but being free.
What was that?
Cannon fire!
Is it the Navy? Can't be.
They're all stuck.
I sewed their ships together extra tight.
Fire!
Columbus can take care of this one.
Sorry, but we're still busy here.
Whoever it is, take them out. Sir!
I know you have Straw Hats on your ship.
Hand them over or pay the price.
You don't want to defy us.
Get back on land! It's dangerous!
But if we leave, Fujitora
might attack Lucy!
Return fire!
Fire!
Let him sink!
Look, the rubble's raining
down on the enemy's ship!
Well, not us!
This is my parting gift, Straw Hat.
Freedom.
Right.
That song Mr.
Luffy wants, it's beautiful.
He's the greatest.
They love him!
Even more!
You know what?
Let's do the oath, because we want to.
It doesn't matter if Straw
Heart won't drink with us.
He makes a good point.
If you can do what you want, so can we.
You wanna talk about freedom?
Well, we have it too!
I didn't think of that!
Mr.
Luffy, I'll raise this sake cup and offer
up an oath. The long-witted? Huh? An oath?
All right, here goes.
We'll become the proud
followers of Straw Hat Luffy.
Therefore, in rain or in shine, we
shall serve as his sword and his shield.
To repay our debt to him, the seven of
us offer a loyalty of our own accord.
As we drink these cups, let us pledge
both our lives and our hearts alike.
I didn't say you guys could do that!
Yeah, I guess it's official now!
Let's get this party started already!
I thought you'd never ask!
Let us feast in honor
of the Straw Hat fleet!
5 ,600 strong! Yeah!
How underhanded.
They just do what they want.
I like their style.
Looking good, Big Boss.
Can't wait to work with you. What?
Hey, I did not drink this stuff.
I know the cup's empty,
but that's not on me.
Yeah, we don't care.
I won't bother trying to force your hand,
but we can still swear our loyalty
to you whether you like it or not.
That means, when you're in
trouble, we'll come running.
If you have friends who are willing
to do that for nothing in return,
you should be grateful.
All we ask is that you engrave
our names and faces on your heart.
Hey, honey.
He's gone.
Look at the main course!
It's a fighting fish steak!
Give me some of that!
Don't climb on poop!
That's unhygienic!
Would you stop crying already?
I was so touched by his
words, I may never stop!
Just leave me to my tears.
Leo, I think we're all
about to leave the port.
Will you stay and eat?
There's no way we'd miss the banquet.
We can take the yellow
cubs back to Dressrosa.
Don't worry about it.
Are we setting sail now?
Right, the bosses, time to go.
Hoist the sail.
I see the rubble raining down.
Did it wipe out Straw Hat and his friends?
No, it's missing all the targets.
You've got to be kidding me.
That day, Dressrosa experienced some
very unusual weather conditions.
But in the end, their heavy downpour of
rubble gradually gave way to sunny skies.
Truth be told, I had no right to
chase you down in the first place.
Also,
Though I probably shouldn't say
this out loud, you really did clean.
up the government's mess here in
Dressrosa And for your courage,
you have my eternal gratitude
I heard that
All right, guys, let's raise our cuffs
Our team kicked the Mingo family's ass!
So here's to us! And...
to victory!
Yeah!
Let's party!
You guys were awesome!
Thanks, Froland!
Sorry, Lind, you're the best! Duh!
Rooster!
Mr. Luffy!
Honey!
Make a toast!
Chew us!
Seems like they made it after all.
I was worried for a sec.
I hope they'll come visit.
Is it warm?
Yes.
It's much better this way.
Oh, are you crying, Dad? What?
No, I never cry.
Don't be absurd.
Wait!
Hey, get over here.
Ow!
Another round?
Yeah, any time.
Let go!
Press nose for advanced hair features.
I know you've got places to go, but
we'll see you again, right? Of course.
We'll be back.
I can't wait!
Great news!
Well, hello.
After the hard-fought battle in Dressrosa,
a very unconventional vow
was made over cups of sake.
By coincidence,
or by the hand of fate,
when the pass of seven mighty warriors
crossed, they pledged their loyalty to Luffy.
Their own adventures will
bring them strength and renown,
and one day in the future,
they will play a part in a great
incident of historic proportions.
But for now, at least, that's a
story no one could have anticipated.